紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯   草草
翻譯   Lynn_寧
翻譯   WalkingNerd
翻譯   鹽湖涼開水
翻譯   章魚埃克斯
時間軸   想念Gallifrey的wholock
后期   餓得慌
校對  草草
顧問  老杜
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第六季  第八集
全劇終
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
克萊爾·黑爾
安德伍德對他妻子的執政能力失去了信心
道格拉斯·斯坦普: 他死的那晚我跟他在一起
前總統安德伍德留有音頻日記
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德泉下之言  我妻子會不擇手段
謝潑德無限責任公司的未來
比爾·謝潑德就總統發表言論
道·斯坦普
我要再發出十條引述
克·安德伍德
別
道·斯坦普
打給我  否則我就發了
道格·斯坦普
道·斯坦普
好夢
雙城記
簡寧
我今天來談談未來
I am here to talk about the future.
未來已經變得極度私人化
And the future has become very personal.
北緯35度28分22秒
35 degrees, 28 minutes, 22 seconds north,
你說什么呢
What are you talking about?
瑞秋·波斯納就埋在那里
It's where Rachel Posner is buried.
痛苦分兩種
There are two kinds of pain.
道格·斯坦普給我發了條信息
Doug Stamper sent me that text,
他說這是你丈夫日記里的話
he said it comes from your husband's diary.
我該采訪你  還是他
who should I interview, you or him?
你已經懷孕26周了  總統女士
You're 26 weeks pregnant, Madam President.
臭婊子  是女孩
You fucking cunt. It's a girl.
她死后  副總統的位子空缺
After her death, with the vice presidency vacant,
我們的朋友布雷特·柯爾會成為總統
our friend Brett Cole will be president.
我們要讓她成為烈士
We'll make her a martyr.
我不在乎你  也不在乎你想要什么
I don't care about you or what you want.
但你確實在乎弗蘭克想要什么
But you do care what Frank wanted.
弗蘭克想讓她死
Frank wanted her dead.
我來找你了  克萊爾
I'm coming for you, Claire.
弗蘭克會怎么辦
What would Frank do?
她可懷著他的孩子呢
Given that she's carrying his child.
我一直承諾會告訴大家真相
I've always promised to tell you the truth.
公開透明是我做總統的基礎
Transparency is the cornerstone of my presidency.
秉持著這一精神
And in that spirit,
我必須把這些事告訴大家
I feel compelled to share the following.
幾周以來
For some weeks now,
司法部在調查幾項指控
the Justice Department has been investigating allegations
前總統  即我丈夫
that the former president, my husband,
故意在幾個州夸大了2016年選舉日的威脅
falsely inflated 2016 election day dangers in several states
可能對選舉結果造成了影響
that may have played a role in tipping the results.
大家可以想象  這一消息
This news, as you can imagine,
讓一個遺孀的心被烏云籠罩
has caused a widow's dark night of the soul.
總統女士
Madam President!
這里曾是我的辦公室
This used to be my office.
那是我的辦公桌
That was my desk.
沙發換了
The couch is different,
但我在這兒過夜的次數多得都數不過來了
but I slept here more nights than I care to remember.
安德伍德議員的辦公桌就在那里
Congressman Underwood's desk was right through there.
他從來不睡
He never slept.
永遠別扣最下面的扣子
Never button the bottom.
-總統女士  -莎拉  請講
- Madam President! - Sarah, yes.
女士  具體來說
Ma'am, to follow up.
您究竟準備采取何種行動
What specific action, if any, are you planning to take,
鑒于您丈夫已經...
since your husband is...
去世了
Dead.
可供考慮的選項有很多
Well, everything is on the table.
包括死后起訴
Up to and including a posthumous indictment.
-拉里  -但是  總統女士
- Larry. - But, Madam President,
如果要質疑選舉結果
if you're calling the election results into question,
那對您的總統之位意味著什么
what does that mean for your presidency?
總統是全國權力最大的職務
This is the highest office in the land.
公職是神圣的
Public service is a sacred privilege,
誰都不能凌駕于法律之上
and no one is above the law.
我孩子的父親不能  我也不能
Not the father of my child, not me.
馬可斯
Marcus.
有人提醒過您剛剛發表的這篇文章嗎
Were you given any warning about this article that just came out?
簡寧·斯克斯基寫的
By Janine Skorsky?
我不知道你指的是什么
I don't know what you're referring to.
是在您講話時發表的
It was posted as you were speaking.
標題是
The headline reads,
《前總統安德伍德將妻子剔出遺囑》
"Former President Underwood excluded his wife from his will."
可以評論一下嗎
Would you care to comment?
我還沒看過的東西  無法作出評論  謝謝
Well, I can't comment on what I haven't seen. Thank you.
文章中提到的線人是道格拉斯·斯坦普
The source named in the piece is Douglas Stamper.
二十多年前  自從道格拉斯
I have known Douglas
成為我丈夫的左右手  我就認識他了
since he became my husband's right hand man over 20 years ago.
他最近飽受折磨  這不是什么秘密
And it is no secret that he's been having a difficult time lately.
最主要的是情緒方面
Emotionally, above all else.
我幾個月前赦免他  是出于憐憫
And when I pardoned him months ago, it was based on compassion.
我同情他  真的
I feel for the man, I do.
但道格·斯坦普絕對無法引導我們發現真相
But Doug Stamper will never be the one to lead us to the truth.
"顯然  前總統在最后時刻手寫了遺囑
"The former president apparently handwrote an 11th hour will,
嚴格說來  是親筆遺囑
technically known as a holographic will,
其中提到將他的全部財產
with instructions that his entire estate
留給前幕僚長道格拉斯·斯坦普"
be left to his former Chief of Staff Douglas Stamper."
寫沒寫到具體內容
Does it say anything about what's in it?
"遺囑的細節尚未公布
"The specifics of the will are not yet public,
但在與斯坦普先生的獨家采訪中
but in an exclusive interview with Mr. Stamper,
他承諾他'很快就會'公開內容"
he promised to reveal the contents 'soon.'"
你可以走了
That'll be all for now.
聯系白宮顧問
Get White House counsel.
不  現在就給我的個人律師打電話
No, no, actually get my personal lawyer on the phone now.
是  女士  還有  格林助理局長來了
Yes, ma'am. And Assistant Director Green is here,
但他堅持要把他的...
but he insisted that his--
總統女士
Madam President.
容我介紹一下我妻子艾比還有我們的兒子杰克遜
Let me introduce you to my wife Abby and this is our son Jackson.
你們好
Hello.
艾比是您的粉絲  我們想跟您合張影
Abby's such a fan, we were hoping to take a picture.
沒問題
Of course.
我希望我的家人陪我一起來告知您
I wanted my family here with me when I let you know,
我要離開聯調局了
I'm leaving the Bureau.
我已經遞交了辭呈
I already submitted my letter of resignation.
納森  那怎么行呢
Nathan, we can't possibly accept that.
求您了  黑爾總統  我求您了
Please, President Hale. I'm begging you.
琳  請進來一下
Lynn, can you come in here, please?
納森  我們必須得單獨談談
Nathan, I insist we speak about this one-on-one.
讓我們單獨談會兒吧
Can you give us a moment?
很抱歉我在沙漠讓你失望了
I'm sorry I failed you as far as the desert,
但我做不下去了
but I can't do this anymore.
-納森  -我已經決定了
- Nathan-- - I've made up my mind.
如果我悄悄離職對我們都好
It's better for both of us if I go quietly.
我想你一定很期待第一天
I'm sure you're looking forward to walking Jackson
送杰克遜上學
to his first day of school.
是的  女士
I am, ma'am.
那我的想法沒改變
Well, my feelings haven't changed.
我希望道格能終于獲得
I want Doug to finally, finally get the help
他非常需要的幫助
he so desperately needs.
你有理由擔憂
You're right to be concerned.
這世上的確有些瘋狂的人
There are some crazy people out there.
我最后跟道格對話時
In my last conversation with Doug,
他告訴我有人找上了他
he told me entities had approached him,
想招募他  艾比
hoping to recruit him. Abby.
你最好取消你接下來的公開露面
You should cancel your upcoming public appearances.
-只是來見老朋友的  -總統說
- Here to see an old friend. - The president said,
"道格·斯坦普絕對無法引導我們發現真相"
"Doug Stamper will never be the one to lead us to the truth."
你想評論嗎
You care to comment?
把我說成是瘋子肯定對總統有利
It must serve the president to paint me as some sort of crazy man.
但抱歉讓她失望了  我頭腦清醒  她很清楚
Bu I'm sorry to disappoint her, I am of right mind, and she knows it.
那份被修改的遺囑  誰知道其內容
In terms of a revised will, who knows about its contents?
這問題你怎么不去問她
Why don't you ask her that question?
先生  你是怎么知道的
Sir, how did you become aware of it?
他死的那晚我跟他在一起
I was with him the night he died.
他叫我去他在海亞當斯酒店的套間
He asked me to his suite at the Hay-Adams.
他說他不再相信
He told me he no longer had faith
他妻子能擔任總統了
in his wife's ability to serve as president.
安德伍德總統
And President Underwood,
真正的安德伍德總統留了音頻日記
the real President Underwood, kept an audio diary.
我已經聽了一些
Pieces of which I've heard.
那我們就找個能做出對我們有利判決的法庭
Then let's find a court that will rule in our favor.
斯坦普  前弗蘭西斯·安德伍德總統的幕僚長
...Stamper, former Chief of Staff to President Francis Underwood,
今天早些時候的言論
recorded earlier today.
我們請嘉賓們
Let's turn to our panel
談談他們怎么看待據稱...
for their take on the claim that the leak--
別忘了  他是個有困擾的人
...remember, this is a troubled man.
我們并不能完全相信他說的一切
We can't take everything he says at face value, right?
問題是  斯坦普究竟有何最終目的
The question is, what is Stamper's endgame here?
-為什么攻擊黑爾總統  -怎么
- Why the whole attack on President Hale... - What?
他是該去激怒她的
He was supposed to provoke her.
他被控謀殺  但最終被開釋
He walked away from murder charges.
-別忘了...  -馬克
- Don't forget that... - Mark...
-我沒時間讀你的心  -我提醒過你
- I don't have time to read your mind. - I tried to warn you.
我跟他合作過  我們有暴露的風險
I've worked with this guy. We could be exposed.
-你相信我嗎  我的直覺  -我當然信你
- Do you trust me, my instincts-- - Yes, of course I do.
但這跟評估他如今帶來的風險毫無關系
That has nothing to do with evaluating the risk he is becoming.
他精神錯亂  安奈特
He's unhinged, Annette.
要的就是精神錯亂
Unhinged is what's called for.
控制好他  那是你的工作
Contain him. That's your job.
安奈特
Annette!
怎么回事
What's going on?
如果我兒子不是我兒子  他早放出來了
If my son were anyone else in this country, he'd be out by now.
不  這算怎么回事
No, what's going on here?
我們之間嗎
Between us?
我們又開始做愛了
We're having sex again.
直到又再次對我們不利
Until it seems like a bad idea, again.
-聽我說  -那賤人
- Hey, listen to me-- - That bitch
在制造對鄧肯不利的局面
is tipping the scales when it comes to Duncan.
他是絕對得不到公正聽證會的
And there's no way he can get a fair hearing,
除非她死了
until she's gone.
好吧  等等
Okay, hold on. Just, um...
你可以退回去一點嗎
Can you back up a few words?
退多少
How far back?
"這種時刻  需要..."
"Moments like this require..."
什么來著
What is it?
"有人采取行動  做一些不好的事"
"Someone who will act. Who will do the unpleasant thing."
可以讓我聽嗎
You know what? Can you just let me hear it?
不行
No.
為什么
Why not?
我不能...
I can't. It's...
你干什么
What are you doing?
沒什么
Nothing, I-- Nothing.
我們不非得這么做的  好嗎
Look, we don't have to go ahead with this. Okay?
不管你需要理清楚什么  你該去理清
And whatever you need to figure out, you should.
你不能就放下他嗎
Like, can't you just leave him alone?
-你當我是什么  -我很清楚你是什么人
- What do you think I am? - Look, I know exactly what you are.
她會找上你的
She's gonna come after you.
"要有人采取行動
"Requires someone who will act.
做一些不好的事  但也是必要的事
Who will do the unpleasant thing, the necessary thing.
別被她美麗的臉騙了
Don't be fooled by her beautiful face.
我妻子很無情"
My wife is ruthless."
"是我認識的最無情的女人  可惜人們不知道"
"The most ruthless woman I've ever met. If people only knew."
我們已申請了禁止令
We've filed an injunction.
但斯克斯基稱她的消息源
But Skorsky's saying her source
認為這些材料是他的
believes the material belongs to him.
這簡直瘋了
This is insane.
除非有人拿出遺囑的證據  沒...
Unless someone produces evidence of a will, there's no--
我們為什么要把這事當真啊
Why are we even taking this seriously?
我相信我可以用噤聲令讓她閉嘴
I am confident I can silence her with a gag order.
但一旦新聞印發
But once a thing is in print,
-其他新聞機構都能...  -印發
- any other news outlet has the right to-- - Print?
這不是紙媒  杰柔丁
This isn't print, Geraldine.
我們不能關閉網站嗎
Can't we just shut down the site?
不能  女士  那恐怕不行
No, ma'am. I don't think we can.
我建議  我們取證
My advice, let's depose.
讓斯坦普先生宣誓
Get Mr. Stamper under oath.
-如果他作偽證  -不  那正中他下懷
- If he perjures himself-- - No. That's exactly what he wants.
他就想要公開的平臺
He wants a public forum.
而且他也受了不少罪了
And he's been through enough already.
總統女士  我得問
Madam President, I have to ask.
我也會在您律師面前提這個問題
And I will ask you this in front of your attorney.
您的立場
Is it your position
是你完全不知道你丈夫...
that you were entirely unaware of your husband's--
-這您不必回答  -不  我想回答
- You don't have to answer that. - No, no, I want to.
我不知道他那么做是為我還是為自己
I don't know if he did it for his sake or mine,
但他從未告訴我任何事
but he never told me a thing.
女士  在美國訴尼克松案中
Ma'am, in United States v. Nixon--
我以他未出世的孩子發誓
I swear on his unborn child.
當然了  公司的部分領域
Well, there's no doubt that there's areas of the company
她并不是很擅長
she's not quite as well versed in.
這我有責任
Partly my fault, our--
我們的父親不相信繼承
Our father didn't believe in succession.
你是說你覺得你妹妹無權...
Are you saying you don't think your sister deserves--
不是  我不是那個意思
No. That's not what I'm saying.
其實  說到繼承
If anything, when I talk about succession,
我想說的是總統之位
I'm talking about this presidency.
承認吧  我們的三軍統帥
Let's face it, our Commander In Chief,
基本上是從她丈夫那里繼承來了這工作
who basically inherited the job from her husband,
還擺出了一副女王的架勢
is acting like a goddamn monarch.
當
When--
當一名暴君假裝透明公開
When a tyrant pretends to be transparent,
國家就要小心了
nation beware.
這些
And these--
這些評論
These comments,
這些道格·斯坦普的公開評論  是完全說得通的
these public comments from Doug Stamper make nothing but sense.
去查串謀吧
I mean, follow the complicity.
-所以你對黑爾總統有什么建議嗎  -有
- So, do you have any advice for President Hale? - Yes.
退位
Abdicate.
-得了  比爾  -不  真的
- Oh. Come on now, Bill. - No, no. Listen
這對國家來說不會是壞事
it wouldn't be the worst thing for this country
如果她的任期提前結束的話
if she didn't finish out her term.
如果那是她的命運的話
If that's what was fated for her.
-謝潑德先生  -聽著
- Mr. Shepard-- - Listen,
我昨晚一個勁地調臺
I was flipping around the channels last night,
然后看到了《邊城英烈傳》
and I came across The Alamo.
我知道那不算部好電影
I know it's not a great movie,
但當約翰·韋恩哽咽著說"共和..."
but when John Wayne chokes up saying "Republic--
比爾·謝潑德  閉上嘴吧
Bill Shepherd, shut the fuck up.
聯系其他人
Reach out to the others.
提醒他們嘴巴不牢的危險
Remind them of the perils of loose lips.
納森·格林參加了一場安奈特·謝潑德主持的會議
Nathan Green was in a meeting hosted by Annette Shepherd.
我不輕易緊張
I don't get rattled easily,
但這件事的秘密性  去的人和為什么去
but the secrecy around this one, who was there and why,
這是我前所未見過的
is more than I have ever come across.
我猜那房間里坐了些很有勢力的人
I suspect there were some very powerful people in that room.
道格拉斯·斯坦普呢
Douglas Stamper?
我還不知道
I don't know yet.
還有別的嗎
Anything else?
沃爾特  你從一開始就跟我們合作
Walter, you have worked with us from the beginning.
是啊  我喜歡弗蘭克
Yes. I liked Frank.
所以我很好奇
So, I'm curious.
你怎么做到的
How did you pull it off?
克萊爾
Oh, Claire,
我的考慮很實際
my calling is a practical one.
我不評判  也不質疑
I don't judge. I don't question.
我只是為出價最高者工作
I simply work for the highest bidder.
我是不可知論者  但這虛擬界對我來說很陌生
I'm agnostic, but this virtual landscape is new to me.
而現在有人
And someone out there
在非常拼命地抹黑弗蘭克
is working very hard to make Frank look very bad.
聽著  現在的雜音很多
Listen, it's just a lot of noise at the moment.
不僅僅是他
It's not only about him.
你要怎么把自己撇干凈啊
How will you manage to separate yourself from all this shit?
現在能聯系到我的只剩道格了
All that's left is Doug to connect me.
小心  克萊爾
Be careful, Claire.
各位啊
Oh, you guys.
我其實真不希望還得這么做的  但是...
I really didn't wanna have to have to do this, but...
哈里發國恐怖組織的一個極端派系
An extreme faction of the ICO terrorist group
企圖在巴基斯坦購買一個核裝置
made an attempt to purchase a nuclear device in Pakistan.
這是事實
That's a fact.
-總統女士  無意冒犯  -瑪莉婭
- Madam President, all due respect-- - Maria,
我知道你是新來的
I know you're new to this,
但請再不要對我用那個俗語了
but please don't ever use that expression with me.
"無意冒犯"表達的是完全相反的意思
"All due respect" means precisely the opposite.
女士  這個威脅
Ma'am, it's just that this threat
仍是一個潛在威脅
remains squarely in the category of a potential--
但他們有意圖
The intent is there.
除非我們能確認交易...
Until we have confirmation that the deal has--
我們的情報機構已經表示
Our intelligence has told us
他們會重新部署  再次嘗試的
that they will regroup and try again.
這能追溯到拉菲克·納澤兩個月前的警告
This goes back to the warning from Rafiq Nasser two months ago.
自從南茜接替了諾拉
Now acting Secretary Gallagher and I
成為代理國土安全部部長
have been keeping a close watch on this threat
我們就一直在密切關注這一威脅
ever since Nancy took over for Nora at Homeland.
為了秉承本屆政府的
And in the spirit of the full transparency
公開透明政策
this administration is embracing,
我們要把這公諸于眾
we're going to take it public.
女士  老實說  我擔心
Ma'am. Frankly, I'm concerned.
從戰略角度講
From a strategic perspective,
如果哈里發國不行動  我們就成了狼來了
if ICO doesn't act, we appear to be crying wolf.
另一方面  我們要把局面搞成
But on the other hand, are we putting ourselves in a position
刺激他們行動嗎
where we're daring them to act?
我們不想魯莽行事
We don't want to appear reckless.
我昨晚睡不著
I couldn't sleep last night.
當然是因為國家安全的原因
For obvious national security reasons, of course,
但是
but...
也因為胎兒鬧得我睡不著
also because the baby kept me awake.
不知怎么
And for some reason...
我想到了"厭女者"一詞
the word "misogynist" popped into my mind.
我努力去想有沒有個對應詞
And I was trying to think of the word for the opposite.
就是討厭男人的專有名詞
You know, the word for when a person hates men.
在場有誰知道那個詞是什么嗎
Does anyone around this table know that word is?
就是討厭男人的專有名詞
The word for when a person hates men?
有人知道嗎
Anybody?
我還去查了一下
I had to go and look it up.
"厭男者"
"Misandrist."
但沒人知道這個詞
And no one really knows that word
因為我們文化中不常用它
because it's not used in our culture.
所以我想說的是  或許我們都
So what I'm getting at, is maybe we all,
不管我們什么性別
regardless of our gender,
應該好好審視一下我們關于誰能
would do well to examine the pre-conceived notions that we have
誰不能做三軍統帥的既定想法
about who can and cannot act as Commander In Chief.
給
There you go.
這家店叫聯邦黨豬
They're from a place called the Federalist Pig.
我沒聽說過
I don't know it.
據說是僅次于弗萊迪的烤肉了
Well, I've been told it is the next best thing to Freddy's.
我不用了  你要點嗎
I'm good. You want some?
不  給你買的
No, they're for you.
道爾在到處打聽你
Doyle has been asking around about you.
我們可以讓他停止
Now we can shut him down.
但是
But...
來吧  給我一根
Yeah, come on, give me one. I mean...
什么樣的人拒絕肋排啊
What kind of man says no to ribs, right?
報道  還有記者招待會
The articles and the press conferences.
雖然不多  但影響很大  道格
A little goes a long way, Doug.
很多人
A lot of people,
可以說整個國家
in a way, the whole country,
-都在指望你  -賽斯
- we're relying on you. - Seth,
我能照顧好自己
I can take care of myself.
可以把醬遞給我嗎
Can you pass that sauce?
你肯定很孤獨
You must be so alone.
你身邊還有值得信任的人嗎
Do you even have anyone around anymore that you can trust?
你在玩什么把戲
What are you playing at?
"她肯定都看見了  所有的殺戮
"Surely, she saw it all. The killing.
相關的謊言"  弗蘭克在第六分鐘說
The lying," Says Frank at minute six.
道格  你和我必須和解
Doug, you and me have to have a come to Jesus.
同意  停止公開指責他  否則就等著被曝光
Agreed. Stop publicly accusing him or it's all gonna come down.
我現在只想尋求事實
All I'm trying to do is seek the truth these days.
76分鐘  "我有大行動前
Minute 76-- "Before I ever made any big moves,
總先跟我妻子商量"
I always ran them by my wife."
我喜歡你的聲音  道格  很安撫人心
I like the sound of your voice, Doug. It's so soothing.
我以前從沒想過這個
I never really thought about it before,
但在這方面  你讓我覺得像弗蘭西斯
but in just this way, you remind me of Francis.
我真正想念的  是他的聲音
The one thing I really miss is his voice.
那一直是我最喜歡他的地方
It was always my favorite thing about him.
不管他說的是什么
No matter what he would say,
他的聲音讓我覺得好像
the sound of his voice made me feel like
一切都會沒事
everything was going to be all right.
不是的
It's not.
除了安奈特  還有誰去了
Besides Annette, who else was there?
只有我能救你  道格
I'm the only one who can save you, Doug.
"他又問我是否不信上帝
"And then he asked if I had no faith in God.
我說  你錯了
I said, 'You have it wrong.
是上帝不信我們"
It's God who has no faith in us.'"
14分鐘  要我給你放嗎
Minute 14. Would you like me to play it for you?
放棄調查  為你對他的抹黑道歉
Drop the investigation and apologize for what you're doing to him
否則就會有更多泄露出來
or more of this is gonna come out.
我要按播放了  我想要你聽聽
I'm gonna press play. I want you to hear it.
我的安全團隊剛告訴我
My security team just informed me
俄羅斯士兵沖美軍特種部隊開槍了  維克多
that Russian soldiers are firing at American Special Forces, Viktor.
是他們入侵了海岸
They invaded the coast,
這違反了你我的協議
which violates agreements you and I made.
是為了防止核裝置
Preventing a nuclear device from--
這是你策劃的嗎  克萊爾
Did you orchestrate this, Claire?
為了什么  分散人們對你丈夫日記的注意
For what? To distract from your husband's diary?
別裝作你不會做出這種事
And don't act like that would be beneath you.
我并不相信當母親能自動讓一個女人變成圣人
I don't believe motherhood automatically makes a woman a saint.
-拉菲克·納澤  -死了
- Rafiq Nasser-- - Is dead.
我們一小時前用無人機襲擊了他
We hit him with a drone strike an hour ago.
他在給我們提供必要的情報
He was providing us with necessary intelligence.
那是你先告訴他的
That you provided him with first.
威脅是真的
The threat is real.
我會讓我格勒烏的人接手的
I'll have my people, the GRU, take it from here.
不行
No, you won't.
克萊爾
Look, Claire, just...
專心生你的孩子去吧
worry about having your baby now.
我一直覺得你的自大很好玩
I've always been entertained by your arrogance.
就像是看已經過了時的電影
It's like watching some movie, just out of date.
如果有危險分子拿到核武器  維克多
If a rogue element gets their hands on a nuclear device, Viktor,
我會先出擊的
I will strike first.
你們那邊現在幾點
What time is it there now?
快日出了吧
Must be close to sunrise, huh?
快了
Just about.
如果你丟原子彈
If you drop an atom bomb,
我們的世界  你女兒的世界
our world, your daughter's world...
太陽會永遠變樣的  克萊爾
That sun will never look the same again, Claire.
你那邊幾點了
What time is it there?
我正要吃午飯
I'm about to have lunch.
你都吃什么
And what are you having?
沙拉
Oh, a salad.
黃瓜和西紅柿  還有羊乳酪
Cucumbers and tomatoes, a bit of feta.
西班牙橄欖  還有丹吉爾的草藥
Some Spanish olive oil and herbs from Tangiers.
我現在不吃面包了
I don't eat bread anymore, you know.
我們還從未好好吃過一頓飯
We never had a proper meal, you and I.
算不上吃過
Not really.
我現在得在聯合國公開反對你了
I'll have to oppose you now, openly at the UN.
事事針對你
And at every turn.
但私下里
Privately, I...
我會想你的
I will miss you.
我已跟佩特羅夫總統說明
As I made clear to President Petrov,
我絕不會允許恐怖分子帶著原子彈
I will not have terrorists waltzing out of the desert
大搖大擺地走出沙漠
with an atomic bomb.
我也該拿你們當大人了
It's time for me to treat you all like the adults you are.
事實就是
The truth is...
我不是唯一有危險的人
I'm not the only one who's in danger.
沒有人真正安全
No one's safe. Not really.
永遠都不
Not ever.
那么會進行核打擊嗎  自長崎后的第一例
Does that mean a nuclear strike? The first one since Nagasaki?
如果有必要的話  是的
If need be, yes.
泰芮
Terry.
你近來公開批評總統
You've become a vocal critic of the president.
甚至在你被捕前
Even before your arrest.
其實  你第一次公開露面
Actually, the first time you went public
就是支持限制她權力的立法
was to support legislation limiting her powers.
而現在這一點更加緊急了
Which is now more urgent than ever.
最近  在你等待庭審時
And recently, as you await trial,
又因為一些言論而陷入了更多麻煩
you got into some more hot water with your comments.
是啊  我失言了
Yes, I misspoke.
但說實話吧  這個總統簡直要命
But let's face it. This president is fatal.
她在刺激末日的到來
I mean, she's out there evoking end of days.
她在任的話
And with her in office,
國家就是會走向末日
that is exactly where this country is headed.
我是什么
And what am I?
因為我還相信家庭  就古板了嗎
Some antiquated soul because I still believe in family?
如果你想改變國家的貧困狀態
Listen, if you want to do something in this country about poverty,
就得靠家庭
family.
減少犯罪  靠家庭
Crime, family.
教育  靠家庭  家庭是一切
Education, family. It's family.
我父母每晚都六點吃飯
My parents had dinner at six o'clock. Every single night.
不管你在哪  在做什么
They didn't care where you were, what the hell you were doing.
晚飯六點開始
Dinner was at six, goddamnit.
你和你妹妹上一次一起吃晚飯是什么時候了
And when's the last time you and your sister had dinner?
這個問題很合理
That is a fair question.
我們的確
And it has been some time
挺久沒有面對面坐下來了
since we sat across from each other.
你好嗎  比爾
How you doing, Bill?
看是哪天了
Depends on the day.
還有用藥劑量
And the dose.
我給你帶了點心來  喬治敦的普蓬
I brought you some pastries, from Poupon, Georgetown.
我知道你就喜歡這個
I know you have a soft spot for those.
我現在不吃糖了
Well, I don't do sugar anymore.
只會助長腫瘤
It's... fuel for the tumor.
你想吃的話吃一個吧
You can have one, if you want.
不用了
No, I'm good.
20年前
Twenty years ago,
我大概會坐下來
I probably would have sat down...
寫本回憶錄
and written out my memoirs,
而不是
instead of...
想盡辦法把話說出去
trying to just get it out there any way I can.
我以為她會來呢
I thought she would have come out.
抱歉  她讓我來了
I'm sorry. She sent me.
她要我停下嗎
Does she want me to stop?
恰恰相反
The opposite.
她要你繼續猛烈抨擊總統
She wants you to keep hitting the president hard...
這樣她就能出來反對你
so that she can come out against you.
這會變得一團亂嗎
Is this gonna be a mess?
可能吧
Could be.
什么時候變成這樣的
When did it happen?
我們成了拼命補救的一方
That we were the ones catching up.
是我們沒留神嗎
Were we not paying attention?
不夠留神
Not enough.
弗蘭西斯就是個混蛋
Francis was a son of a bitch.
但他是個厲害的混蛋
But he was a talented son of a bitch.
他料到了她
He saw her coming.
卻阻止不了他自己
He just couldn't stop himself.
或她
Or her.
你覺得十年后我們會變成什么樣  馬克
Where do you think we're gonna be in ten years, Mark?
拜托  這個問題我逢人便問
Come on. I'm asking everybody.
-因為顯而易見的原因  -你比我更常想這個
- For obvious reasons. - You think about it more than I do.
大腹便便  醉眼迷離  心不在焉
Fat, wasted and distracted.
這么過一晚還不錯  但不能這么生活
Might be a good night out, but it's no way to live a life.
拜托  十年后
Come on, ten years?
我不知道
I don't know.
事情并不會怎么改變  比爾
Things don't really change, Bill.
只會...
They just--
只會逐漸消逝  兄弟
They just fade away, man.
天啊  我真憤怒
God, I'm angry.
我聽了你丈夫的錄音
I heard your husband's voice.
道格拉斯·斯坦普來找我們
Douglas Stamper came to us.
要把弗蘭西斯的日記給我們
Offered up Francis' diaries,
道格給我放了部分片段
snippets of which Doug played for me.
說實話  我想過拿它對付你
And to tell you the truth, I considered using it against you.
但我覺得錄音
But I don't think it should
不應該被公開
ever find its way into the public sphere.
-我很驚訝  -我不是我哥哥
- Forgive my surprise. - I'm not my brother.
比爾現在對民主是不利的
Bill's become bad for democracy.
和之前的弗蘭西斯一樣
Like Francis was.
大家都喜歡看女生打架
The world loves a cat fight,
但我說我們不要如他們的愿
but I say let's deny them the satisfaction.
對我們來說還不算太遲
It's not too late for us.
你說得對  我們不要讓他們如愿
You know, you're right. Let's not give them what they want.
去他們的
Fuck them all.
抱歉  寶貝
Sorry, Angel.
他們是能聽到聲音的  有這方面的研究
They hear things, you know. There have been studies.
感覺是不是很棒
Is it amazing?
是的
It is.
她是個活潑的小東西
She's an active little thing.
我可以摸摸嗎
May I?
當然可以
Sure.
她在踢我
She's kicking.
我們會解決掉道格的
We'll take care of Doug.
我不相信你會支持我
I don't believe your support.
你根本不會說謊  安妮
You're a bad liar, Annie.
你還企圖殺了她
And you tried to kill her.
你手里有我兒子
You have my son.
你準備怎么下手
How are you gonna do it?
我不知道你在說什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
告訴我其他人是誰  我就放了鄧肯
Tell me who the others are and I will let Duncan go.
-他是無辜的  和我一樣  -天啊  得了
- He's innocent, as am I. - God, please.
這所謂的核危機
This so-called nuclear crisis.
你比弗蘭克還糟糕
You're worse than Frank.
她又在踢我了
She's kicking again.
像是她感覺到  結局就快到了
It's like she senses we're nearing the end.
唯一的問題是  道格
The only question, Doug, is
如果你是他們的A計劃  那他們的B計劃是什么
if you're their plan A, what's their plan B?
如果弗蘭西斯還在  我們就能知道
If Francis were here, we'd know.
是啊  如果他準備殺我
Yes. Well, if he was going to kill me,
-他會怎么做  -他會利用你提供的機會
- how would he do it? - He'd find an opportunity you provided.
他總是搶先人三步  是吧
He was always three steps ahead, wasn't he?
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德...
Francis Underwood...
也許他現在還是這樣
Maybe he still is.
我一直在延續他的生命嗎
Have I been keeping him alive?
我愿意走到哪一步
Just how far am I willing to go?
我有些猶豫了
I'm having second thoughts.
我確定這是個好主意嗎
Am I sure this is a good idea?
是的
Yes.
如果我懷的是惡魔的種呢
What if I'm carrying a demon seed or something?
五五開的幾率
The odds are 50-50.
真是受夠了說弗蘭西斯的事
So tired of talking about Francis.
我想念我男朋友里德
I miss my boyfriend Reed.
我有時候也想  但...
I do too, sometimes, but--
里德想要的太多
Reed wanted too much.
弗蘭西斯允許我保持饑餓
Francis gave me permission to hunger.
因為他也是這樣
Because he felt it himself.
一直都不滿足
All the time. Insatiable.
大家都覺得我應該知足了
Everyone thinks I should feel sated.
而他說  "不  克萊爾
Then he said, "No, Claire,
和我一樣饑餓  永不滿足"
be as hungry as me."
于是我吞噬了他
And so I ate him?
他吞噬了自己
He ate himself.
道格·斯坦普呢
Doug Stamper?
我也要吞噬他嗎
Am I going to eat him?
-上帝先生  -魔鬼先生
- Herr God. - Herr Lucifer.
出自《拉撒路夫人》一詩
當心了
Beware.
我一直以為
You know, I always thought...
-或許某一天...  -放回去
- maybe one day, you know, but... - Put it back.
什么
What?
那張照片  貼回冰箱上
The picture. It belongs on the fridge.
好  抱歉
Okay, sorry.
如果有什么我可以做的
You know, if there is anything that I can do.
萬一沒能如我們的愿
I mean, in case it doesn't go as planned.
能別晃來晃去嗎
Can you please stop moving?
我有點緊張  好嗎
I'm a little worked up, all right?
克萊爾·黑爾·安德伍德生而后死
Claire Hale Underwood lived and then she died.
-她也只是凡人  -沒錯
- She's no different from anyone else. - Yeah.
我不敢說世人會和你持相同的看法
Well, I'm not sure the world's gonna see it the way you do.
如果一切順利  你將成為英雄
If this breaks right, you can be a hero.
別拍馬屁了  賽斯
Don't spin me, Seth.
他們打算怎么處理我
How do they plan to do me in?
賽斯
Seth?
聽著
Look.
我這么說
I'm gonna say this to you.
并不是因為我們是朋友
Not because we're friends.
而是因為我們一起經歷的一切
But because of everything that we've been through together.
你是個混賬
You're an asshole.
你如果不想做  可以退出
You don't have to be a part of this, if you don't want to.
你這么說是為了我  還是為了自己
You saying that for me or for you?
或許都是
Maybe both.
我不清楚是誰
I don't know who it is...
但他們在白宮有內應
but they have someone inside the White House.
軍方一向看她不順眼
Military always hated her.
那是一點
That's one thing.
去他們的
Fuck 'em all.
我們倆就遠走高飛吧
What about the two of us? We just leave.
你想去哪里
Where do you wanna go?
喂
Hello.
他看起來如何
How does he look?
挺好  他肯定她會邀請他去
He's fine. He's sure that she'll invite him in.
讓他接電話
Put him on.
道格
Doug.
嗯
Yeah.
多么偉大的時刻
What extraordinary times these are.
我真希望能親自握你的手
I wish I could be there to shake your hand.
安奈特  有件事我必須講明
Annette, I want to make something very clear.
我這么做不是為了你
I'm not doing this for you.
我們一定會把他從加夫尼遷到阿靈頓公墓
We'll be sure to move him from Gaffney to Arlington.
并且資助圖書館
And help fund the Library.
道格  考慮到你近期的精神狀態
And, Doug, given your recent struggles,
九年十年后  你就能出來了
nine or ten years from now, you could be out.
我要感謝你
And I want to thank you.
賽斯
Seth.
是
Yes.
這邊已經準備就緒
Everything is set from our side.
只差臨門一腳了
The quarterback is standing by.
鄧肯呢
And Duncan?
他只能等了
Is going to have to wait.
她還說了什么
What else did she say?
沒了
Nothing.
就...
Just...
一切都準備好了
everything's in place.
再見
Later.
賽斯
Seth.
事情發展不會如你所想的
It's not going to go like you think.
不
No.
我從來就不喜歡對你說話
I never liked talking to you in the first place.
據我得到消息
From what I hear,
你取消公開露面是對的
you were right to cancel your public appearances.
-你這么認為  -是的  女士
- You think so? - I do, ma'am.
我認為你目前待在白宮里
I think the White House is the safest place
是最安全的
for you to be right now.
納森  你是個騙子
Nathan, you're a liar.
幫我個忙  替我親吻你小寶寶的額頭
Do me a favor. Kiss your sweet baby's forehead for me.
我們的情報已證實
Our intelligence confirms
交易馬上就要進行了
the hand off is on the verge of taking place.
但我們的情報顯示并非如此
And our intelligence says that's not so.
這可是一片半徑20英里的沙地
We're talking about a 20-mile radius of sand.
無法通過常規辦法到達
Unreachable by conventional means.
我會讓我的部隊配合你的部隊  好嗎
I'll have my forces coordinate with yours, okay?
我沒在請求準許  維克多
I'm not asking for your permission, Viktor.
克萊爾  我能看出你多么渴望讓敵人知道
Look, Claire. I can see how eager you are to show your enemies
你有多強大
just how powerful you are.
但是  拜托
But, please,
不要這樣做
please don't do this.
我了解你
I know you,
知道你做過的事
the things you've done.
想想世界會如何評價你
Think how the world will judge you.
就好像你在世界舞臺上有什么可信度似的
As if you have any credibility with the world stage.
準備一份聲明
Prepare a statement.
女士  我必須反對
Ma'am, I need to object.
你說什么
Pardon me?
民眾知道我們準備進行核打擊了
The public is aware we're prepared to strike.
我們不需要讓他們更加恐慌了
We don't need to alarm them further.
我不要參與這出戲
I will not be a part of this... this fabrication.
通知軍隊副官
Alert the military aide.
我要他準備好核公文包等著我
I want him ready and waiting with the briefcase.
一次針對性的打擊將使該地區
A targeted strike will destabilize the region
動蕩幾十年
for decades to come...
還會在歐洲
and it will create a distrust
和亞洲大部分地區產生不信任感
that will ripple through Europe and much of Asia.
市場將受到震蕩  是的  后果會很嚴重
Markets will be rocked. Yes, the consequences will be grave.
但我已經得知
But it has come to my attention...
現在有針對我的陰謀
that there is a plot against me.
我的白宮里有人打算背叛我
Someone in my White House is planning to betray me.
在我找出內鬼之前
And until I find out who that is,
我不會重新考慮我的立場
I will not reconsider my position here.
女士  道格·斯坦普給您送來了一樣東西
Ma'am? Something arrived for you from Doug Stamper.
它通過了安檢
It was passed through security.
謝謝
Thank you.
說
Yes.
軍人不支持你
The men in uniform don't support you.
把白宮清場
I want the White House emptied out.
除了你們  只留下必要的最少人手
Other than yourselves, minimal and essential staff only.
-所有來訪者都要經過我的同意  -是  女士
- All visitors need to be cleared by me. - Yes, ma'am.
你在開玩笑嗎  你要放我鴿子嗎
Are you fucking kidding me? Are you standing me up?
上帝保佑你
God bless you, man.
但你不是這樣答應我的
But this is not what you promised me.
你可以告訴總統
And you can tell the president
她可以派一幫律師對付我
that she can send an army of lawyers at me,
但別想埋了我
but I won't be buried.
我不會罷休的
I am not going to stop.
我不知道在什么時候以何種方式
And I don't know when it will be or how.
但我一定會完成這該死的報道  好嗎
But I am going to finish this godforsaken story, okay?
看  哈利·布洛克的畫  這是我最喜歡的
See, the Harry Brooker painting, that's my very favorite.
然后是霍格斯
And then there's the Hogarth.
18世紀  英國的
That's 1700's, English.
還有法國的  夏爾丹  同一時期
And from France, the Chardin, same period.
紙牌屋
Maison des Cartes.
還有一幅...
There's...
19世紀  德國的
one from the 1800s from Germany
這個很有趣
that's very interesting in here.
在這里  看到了嗎
There, see?
它們都有一個共同點
They all have one thing in common.
兒童在觀看
Children watching,
等待紙牌掉下來[等待結果]
waiting for the cards to fall.
賽斯·格雷森
Seth Grayson.
安奈特
Annette.
我不要在這兒等著
I won't be here for this.
那你想去哪里
Where would you rather be?
我不知道
I don't know.
1999年
1999.
芝加哥南部  租戶擁護小組
Tenants Advocacy Group, south side of Chicago.
但我又去不了  所以我不知道
But I can't be there, so I don't know.
如果你要離開  就快走
If you're leaving, leave.
女士
Ma'am.
謝謝你  弗洛拉上校
Thank you, Colonel Flora.
他們對你承諾了什么
What did they promise you?
-女士  我沒有...  -閉嘴
- Ma'am, I didn't-- - Quiet.
你怎么這么久才來
What took you so long?
能讓我們單獨談談嗎
May we have the room, please?
-您確定嗎  女士  -沒事的  謝謝
- Are you sure, ma'am? - Yes. It's all right. Thank you.
道格
Doug.
要喝一杯嗎
Do we need a drink?
你不能喝酒
You can't.
畢竟是非常時刻  是吧
Well, desperate times, right?
這些是想殺了你的人
Here's who wants you dead.
安奈特·謝潑德讓我在外面等
Annette Shepherd had me waiting.
我知道都誰去了
I know who was there.
謝謝
Thank you.
不管這里發生什么
Whatever happens here...
你知我知
It's between us.
道格  我了解你  你從來擁有過誰
Doug, I know you. You've never really had anyone else.
有個瑞秋·波斯納  不過
Rachel Posner, but...
你覺得那件事  你還能逃避多久
How long do you think you're going to get away with that?
我逃不了
I don't.
你打算給她起什么名字
What are you going to call her?
還沒定
I haven't decided yet.
-你覺得呢  -弗蘭西絲·安德伍德
- What do you think? - Frances Underwood.
絲綢的絲
Frances with an "E."
那是給她的
That belongs to her.
她會聽到他的聲音  他的話嗎
She ever gonna get to hear his voice? His words?
不會
No.
也永遠不會有人聽到了
And neither is anyone else.
-她父親是個偉人  克萊爾  -道格
- Her father was a great man, Claire. - Doug.
他在這些錄音里  有多少次
How many times did he even mention your name
提到過你的名字
in those recordings?
-他是在保護我  -不是
- He was protecting me. - No.
你非要這么認為  我很遺憾
I'm so sorry you need to believe that.
你想要嗎
Do you want it?
了解你的人  只剩下我了  克萊爾
I'm the only one left who knows you, Claire.
你利用這個孩子
You're using that child out there,
裝出一副國母的樣子
acting like the mother of this nation.
-但我知道真相  -道格  我很幸福
- I know the truth. - Doug, I'm happy.
相信我  我如魚得水
Believe me. I'm good.
我想告訴你  我原諒你了
I want you to know that I forgive you.
是你做的  是不是
It was you, right?
他過來是想殺了你
He was coming here to kill you.
然后下一個目標就是你
And then he was going to go to you next.
我不能讓你毀了他
I couldn't let you destroy him.
你是想讓他死在我床上  你是這么計劃的嗎
Did you want him to die in my bed? Was that your plan?
我哪有什么計劃
I didn't have a plan.
我根本不知道
I didn't know.
我真的不知道
I didn't-- I didn't know.
我用了他的藥
I used his meds.
我不知道要花多久才生效  但是我
I didn't know how long it would take, but I--
我知道
I knew.
我不能讓他毀掉我們成就的一切
I couldn't let him destroy everything we built.
我必須阻止他破壞他的遺產
I had to protect the legacy from the man.
他變弱了  道格
He got weak, Doug.
這不是你的錯
That wasn't your fault.
是他成就了你
He made you!
說啊  說啊
Say it. Say it.
快說
Say it.
我不會如你所愿的
I'm not going to give you what you want.
可惡  克萊爾  說吧  求你了
Damn it, Claire. Just say it. Please.
他死了  你也很開心吧
You're happy he's dead, too.
那就說  說啊
Then say it! Say it!
快說
Say it!
現在就說
Say it right now.
忘了他吧  道格
Let him go, Doug.
我做不到
I can't!
對不起
I'm sorry.
我很抱...
I'm sor--
沒事了
It's okay.
沒事了  沒事了
It's okay. It's okay.
沒事
It's okay.
對不起
I'm sorry.
沒事了  道格
It's all right, Doug.
一切都會沒事的
Everything is gonna be all right.
It's all gonna be all right.
好了
There.
沒有痛苦了
No more pain.
2013年美版《紙牌屋》第一季上線  隨后在當年的艾美獎上獲得9項提名
成為美國電視史上第一部獲得艾美獎提名的網絡劇  在過去5年中
《紙牌屋》共獲得46項艾美獎提名和8項金球獎提名  包括最佳劇集
男女主演凱文·史派西和羅賓·萊特都曾憑在本劇中的表演獲得過金球獎
但與其它經典美劇不同的是  《紙牌屋》的成功
深深影響了美國娛樂工業在21世紀的發展  其歷史地位遠超一部普通電視劇
網飛當年冒著巨大風險  投資1億美元制作了《紙牌屋》第一季
進入了自主制作內容的領域  并破天荒地采取一次性整季上線的發行方式
由于編導演俱佳  該劇上線后非常成功  網飛也加大了原創劇方面的投入
到2018年  其在自主內容制作上的投資預算已經達到了驚人的130億美元
在2018年的艾美獎上  網飛超過HBO獲得了112項提名  并最終奪得23個獎項
《紙牌屋》第六季上線前幾天  網飛還宣布了一項新的發行政策
其自主制作的幾部優質影片上線前  將先在一些線下影院放映
該政策是為了讓這幾部佳作能夠有資格參加明年的奧斯卡最佳影片競爭
《紙牌屋》的成功和網飛的飛速擴張  徹底改變了全球劇迷觀看視頻節目的習慣
也讓美國娛樂工業發生了滄海桑田般的變化
亞馬遜  Hulu  甚至蘋果等公司開始投巨資進入自主制作在線視頻內容的領域
HBO  STARZ  ShowTime等有線付費頻道也隨之加大投入  改變制作發行方式
迪士尼收購20世紀福克斯  試圖推出自己的在線付費服務等
都很大程度上是為了應對網飛的競爭威脅
《紙牌屋》2013年第一季上線時  網飛的付費用戶是三千六百萬
到2018年  網飛在全球一百多個國家提供服務  用戶總數達到一億三千七百萬
現在每天全球互聯網有15%的流量是在播放網飛的劇集
網飛也從一家在線視頻網站  發展成了全球最大的娛樂媒體公司
但元老劇集《紙牌屋》卻漸漸失去了曾經的光環
最后幾季很少獲得獎項肯定  粉絲口碑也有所下降  除了劇集本身的質量問題
《紙牌屋》的降溫  還因為美國所有政治劇創作者都面臨的一個巨大挑戰：
現實生活中的美國政治越來越離譜  美劇的內容還不如電視新聞精彩
美國政壇亂象的夸張離譜  讓美劇編劇們只能自嘆不如